<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Joisah Brown</title>
    <link>https://JosiahABrown.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Joisah Brown</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 12:18:10 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://JosiahABrown.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Go Basics: Why You Should Learn Go in 2023</title>
      <link>https://JosiahABrown.github.io/posts/2023/01/go-basics-why-you-should-learn-go-in-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 12:18:10 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://JosiahABrown.github.io/posts/2023/01/go-basics-why-you-should-learn-go-in-2023/</guid>
      <description>Go, also known as Golang, is a popular programming language developed by Google in 2007. It is known for its simplicity, concurrency support, and efficient memory management.
Go is a compiled, statically-typed language that is designed to be easy to read and write, while still providing the performance and scalability needed for modern software development.
One of its unique features is its support for concurrent programming, making it well-suited for tasks such as network servers and distributed systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://JosiahABrown.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://JosiahABrown.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I am an experienced software developer skilled in designing, installing, testing, and maintaining software systems. Passionate about scripting, I create efficient solutions tailored to the unique needs of organizations. I have experience in unit testing, automation, Docker, Git and Amazon Web Services. Committed to furthering the mission of any company I work for, and willing to share my knowledge and experience with my colleagues. I am always looking for new opportunities to put my skills to work.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
